https://www.communityfoundationfrv.org/privacy-policy/

Effective Date: July 8, 2008
The Community Foundation of the Fox River Valley is committed to safeguarding your privacy. This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) explains the way information is collected and used on this web site. For easy and direct access, we provide a link to this Privacy Policy from our home page and all other pages of the site.
Changes To This Policy
In the event that the Foundation changes this Privacy Policy, the changes will be updated and the effective date will be revised accordingly.
Collection and Use of Personal and Anonymous Information
Visitors to the site may access information while remaining anonymous.  We do not require you to register or provide personal information to view the site.  There are occasions when you will be asked for additional information.  This is in response to your needs, in an effort to provide you with services that you have requested.  For example, contact information will be requested when you make a donation to the Foundation using our secure, online contribution form.  This information is used to process your contribution.  We may also use this information to contact you in the future with additional information that may be of interest to you.
Cookies
A cookie is computer code placed on your hard drive when you visit the site.   We may use cookies to help us recognize you when you come back to the site.  We may also use cookies to monitor traffic on our site.  This will help us better develop the site and tailor it to the needs of our visitors.  Some browsers may enable you to refuse cookies, which you may do, but please note that navigation on the site may become more difficult if you choose to do so.
IP Addresses and Demographics
The site may collect information through IP addresses or demographic variables.  An “IP address” is a number used by computers on the network to identify your computer so that data can be transmitted to you.  “Demographic variables” include, among other things, the domain from which you access the internet, the time you accessed the site, type of web browser and operating system or platform used, the internet address of the web site you visited to link to the site, the names of the pages you visit while visiting the site, and the internet address of the web site you then visit.   We collect all of this information to allow us to monitor broad demographic trends, to provide information tailored to your interests, and to enhance your experience on the site.
Sharing of Information
The Foundation does not share Donor Information with any third party.
Grantee information may be shared with third parties for a variety of purposes, including but not limited to the marketing of goods and services, disclosure of use of public funds, and project conservation outcomes for the purposes of bettering conservation.  Some grantee Information will also be accessible and searchable to visitors to the site (i.e., project name, description, funding information).  This information is intended as a public resource for conservation and for perspective grantees when filing proposals to the Foundation. If you do not wish your information to be used in that manner, contact us prior to submitting an application for instructions for opting out. If you’re a grantee that wishes to remove its information from our web site, please send an e-mail to:  info@CommunityFoundationFRV.org.
Links to Third Party Sites
This web site provides links to third party sites that may have privacy policies that differ from ours.  You should review the privacy policies posted on each site.
Feedback
The Foundation welcomes comments and questions about this Privacy Policy.  We are committed to securing your personal information and will make every reasonable effort to keep that information protected.
Opt-Out
You may request that we delete your information or refrain from contacting you further by sending us an email to this address:  info@CommunityFoundationFRV.org.  Please note that this opt-out policy does not apply to Grantee Information or that it may not be possible to delete all copies of the information as some of it may be contained on back-up disks or in legally-required records.  Nevertheless, we will strive to honor your request to the best of our ability.
Security
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.  No system is impenetrable, however, and the Foundation will not guarantee absolute security of the information in our possession.
All credit card transactions are conducted over a secure server.  If you do not wish to make a donation online, please contact us at (630) 896-7800 and we will provide alternative methods for you.
Contact Us
Please use the following address for all communication and contributions with the Foundation, including e-mail, postal service, and telephone:
Community Foundation of the Fox River Valley
111 West Downer Place, Suite 312
Aurora, Illinois 60506
info@CommunityFoundationFRV.org
(630) 896-7800
Children’s Information
Most pages on the site are designed for a general audience.  On those pages, we do not knowingly collect information about children.  Should we become aware that a child under 13 has submitted personally identifiable information in a manner that is not compliant with this Privacy Policy, we will delete it immediately.  We do not accept donations from individuals under 18 years of age.
A Note to Kids
The Foundation encourages you to get permission from your parents before sending any information about yourself over the Internet, to us or to anyone else.
A Note To Parents
PLEASE READ. This section of the privacy policy explains our information collection and use practices online for children under the age of thirteen, including what we do with information that we collect and with whom we share that information. We ask that you take the time to review our policy so that you can know exactly how we collect and use information from kids, and so that you will know how you can review or request that we delete your child’s information. If you ever have any questions or concerns about this policy, please contact us at:   (630) 896-7800.  This privacy policy is intended to comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”).
What Information We Collect From Children Under Thirteen
Except as provided herein, personal information from children under thirteen years of age is not collected on the site without parental consent.
As a parent or guardian, you may exercise your right to have your child’s information deleted at any time. Additionally, you may review your child’s personally identifiable information at any time. See Parent’s Rights, below.
How We Use Information We Collect From Children Under Thirteen
When we collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen, we will use that information only for the express purpose for which it was collected.  The information will not be used for any other purpose and the information will not be used after a request to delete the information has been received from the child or you.
We do not share information collected from children under the age of thirteen with any third parties except those parties that help us administer the site. These third parties may not use the information for any other purpose, and have agreed to maintain the confidentiality, security and integrity of the information.  The following company has agreed and complies with this policy:
WebLinx Inc.
165 Kirkland Circle
Oswego, Illinois 60543
Additionally, in the unlikely event that all, or substantially all, of our assets are sold or transferred to another party, all email addresses collected and saved by us may be transferred to the acquiring party. Finally, we may disclose your child’s email address to third parties in order to comply with the law, to law enforcement agencies, to protect our rights in or the safety of the site, or to protect the safety or rights of other users of the site.
Cookies and Non-Personally Identifiable Information
To help make the site more responsive to the needs of our visitors, we invoke a standard feature found in browser software, called a “cookie,” to assign each visitor a unique, random number, a sort of anonymous user ID that resides on your computer. The cookie doesn’t actually identify the visitor, just the computer that a visitor uses to access our site. A cookie can’t read data off your hard drive. We do not link cookie data with personally identifiable information, nor do we store a child’s personal information in our cookies. You can disable cookies at any time by changing the preferences in your browser.
Finally, records of certain non-personally identifiable information such as the number of hits a Web page receives, IP address, and other aggregate data are maintained via the site. We do not link this aggregate data with any personal information. Third parties that help us administer the site may have access to this non-personally identifiable, aggregate data. However, these third parties are bound to keep this information confidential.
Parent’s Rights
We want you to be comfortable with what your child is doing on the site. Therefore, you may contact the Foundation at any time regarding privacy questions or concerns, or to request to review personally identifiable information we have collected from your child. You may also contact us at any time to request that we delete your child’s personally identifiable information, and/or refuse to permit further collection or use of your child’s information. We will take steps to ensure that any person contacting us for a child’s information is that child’s parent or guardian.
Officers, Directors And Staff
Service Area
Communications
Annual Reports
eNewsletters
Newsletters
Press
History
